<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Abouts on </title>
    <link>/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Abouts on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Apache License 2.0</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 20:14:03 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Legal</title>
      <link>/about/legal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 20:14:03 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/legal/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;This page introduces the Terms and Conditions of Koliseo, a platform that lets you organize the agenda, feedback, and tickets for your events. &lt;a href=&#34;/about/legal-es/&#34;&gt;Go to the Spanish version&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;business-identification:7d11b95da6f13f352e32f5af2c24f251&#34;&gt;Business Identification&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;layman-terms&#34;&gt;In which we explain who we are and where we can be found&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Extrema Sistemas, S.L., owner of the website &lt;a href=&#34;http://koliseo.com&#34;&gt;http://koliseo.com&lt;/a&gt; (hereinafter Koliseo) residing
at 24A Casas de Miravete St., 28031 Madrid; with CIF B38676615, registered in the Commercial Register
of the Community of Madrid, Volume 29.041, sheet 109, section 8, page M-522980 eighth
registration. (hereinafter Extrema Sistemas).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These conditions govern the access and use of the service that Koliseo offers to all Internet Users. Any inquiries may be directed to the address: info@koliseo.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;acceptance-of-terms-of-use:7d11b95da6f13f352e32f5af2c24f251&#34;&gt;Acceptance of Terms of Use&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;layman-terms&#34;&gt;In which we make clear that in order to use this website these conditions must first be accepted.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Individuals that make use of Koliseo (hereinafter Users) should read the present Terms and Conditions. The use or access to Koliseo implies the knowledge and full acceptance of the legal warnings and conditions detailed below. Extrema Sistemas reserves the right to modify these Terms of Use on their own initiative and without prior notice to the User, such requirements entering into force from the time of publication on the web and applied retroactively.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Extrema Sistemas reserves the right to change without prior notice the design, layout and configuration of Koliseo, as well as any existing or new services. Also, Extrema Sistemas reserves the right to, at any time and without notice, deny access to this site to those Users who violate any of these legal conditions or the particular ones that apply to them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The acceptance of this disclaimer entails the creation of a Legal Agreement with binding effects between Extrema Sistemas and the User. By using Koliseo, the User accepts the User Terms and Conditions (hereinafter the Terms and Conditions) set out below, and agree that the User has the legal capacity to enter and respond by this Agreement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;purpose-of-the-website:7d11b95da6f13f352e32f5af2c24f251&#34;&gt;Purpose of the website&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;layman-terms&#34;&gt;In which we explain that our goal is to sell tickets and promote interaction among users.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The purpose of Koliseo is to provide our Users with the best possible experience in the purchase of tickets for their events. This experience comes along with event management tools and features to share opinions with other Users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Extrema Sistemas acts as a ticketing agent authorized to sell tickets on behalf of the organizer (hereinafter Organizer) that organizes the event for which the User acquires a ticket. Extrema Sistemas may share with the Organizer personal information of the Users that have purchased tickets. Extrema Sistemas may use data from the User to contact him when necessary, concerning the transactions entered by the User in Koliseo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;user-obligations:7d11b95da6f13f352e32f5af2c24f251&#34;&gt;User obligations&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;layman-terms&#34;&gt;In which the age limit and permitted uses of Koliseo are specified.  It is not allowed to send spam, spread information against morality or reselling tickets. When in doubt, common sense tends to do well.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;register-in-the-system:7d11b95da6f13f352e32f5af2c24f251&#34;&gt;Register in the system&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Koliseo does not store user credentials, and instead delegates in third-party authentication systems. The first time a user logs into Koliseo, the server creates a User Account. The login page clearly states that by logging into the system, the User expresses acceptance of these Terms and Conditions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The minimum age requirement to use Koliseo is 14 years old. The minor children should always ask and get permission from their parents, guardian or legal representative before accessing Koliseo. It is prohibited the access and use to minors that are not authorized. Extrema Sistemas understands that when a minor accesses Koliseo he has the permission of parents, guardian or legal representative. As legal guardian of the children in their care, remember that Koliseo may incorporate information aiming at a diverse audience, and therefore there may be specific areas or sections that include content or comments inappropriate to the minors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Extrema Sistemas cannot validate the accuracy of data entered and is not responsible for any Users distorting the data. Extrema Sistemas will proceed to block any Users that are found not to meet the minimum legal age or have misrepresented any other data.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;personal-information:7d11b95da6f13f352e32f5af2c24f251&#34;&gt;Personal information&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Koliseo collects the personal information necessary to perform our functions. You can read more about &lt;a href=&#34;/about/privacy/&#34;&gt;our Privacy Policy&lt;/a&gt;, including our use of Cookies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When a User registers for an event, they are giving consent to provide their personal data to the organizer of such event, which may not be bound to treat your personal data in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Extrema Sistemas is not responsible for the actions of these Organizers with respect to their personal data.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;ticket-purchase:7d11b95da6f13f352e32f5af2c24f251&#34;&gt;Ticket purchase&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order to make the purchase of tickets, the User declares to be an adult (18 years old or more, depending on applicable law) with the legal capacity to purchase tickets through Koliseo, stating that they accept being bound by this Agreement and understands and accepts all the conditions set forth here for using Koliseo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The event organizer reserves the right of admission for Users in violation of norms of the venue. In a timely manner, the organizer shall make safety inspections to ensure the safety of customers. Attendees arriving late will be accommodated during a suitable break of the event, but admission will not always be guaranteed in this case. The company is not liable for any lost or stolen tickets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;forbidden-uses:7d11b95da6f13f352e32f5af2c24f251&#34;&gt;Forbidden uses&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The User agrees to use the services provided by Koliseo in accordance with the Law and these Terms and Conditions, and must refrain from using them to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Transmit to unauthorized third parties your username and password.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Upload to the web computer programs capable of causing damage to computer systems belonging to Koliseo, its suppliers or third parties.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform illegal activities or contrary to good faith, customs, moral or public order.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Carry out activities in breach of regulations on intellectual and industrial property or other applicable legal standards.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Spread contents that are racist, xenophobic, pornographic, erotic, promoting terrorism or violating human rights.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Harassing another person.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform spamming practices and, in general, disseminate unsolicited or unauthorized advertising, promotional materials, &amp;ldquo;junk mail&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;chain letters&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;pyramid schemes&amp;rdquo; or any other form of information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Engage in commercial activities without written consent from Extrema Sistemas. Swaps, betting, advertising, resale of tickets, etc. will be considered as commercial activities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The User understands and agrees that without prior notice Extrema Sistemas may terminate their access to Koliseo, cancel any tickets or remove any User content that Extrema Sistemas believes has violated or is inconsistent with the Terms of Use, or constitutes an infringement of the rights of Extrema Sistemas, other Users or the Law.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;exclusion-of-liability:7d11b95da6f13f352e32f5af2c24f251&#34;&gt;Exclusion of Liability&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;layman-terms&#34;&gt;In which we clarify that we are going to make mistakes because this system is being developed by humans. However, we keep working hard to make errors memorable as a funny anecdote.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The User acknowledges that it is not technically possible to achieve 100% uptime of Koliseo. Extrema Sistemas does not guarantee the availability and continuity of the service. Extrema Sistemas will not be liable for damages of any kind that may be due to lack of availability or fraudulent use that Users could have made of Koliseo. Extrema Sistemas does not assume any responsibility for any problems accessing the pages of Koliseo. However, Extrema Sistemas will strive to maintain the availability of Koliseo as continuously as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Extrema Sistemas cannot guarantee that files downloaded by the User are free of viruses or malicious files. Extrema Sistemas will not be liable for any damages caused by using Koliseo, including without limitation direct, indirect, incidental, punitive and consequential damages. Extrema Sistemas is not responsible for the products, services, actions or inaction of any venue, artist, producer or third party related to the Web or to which reference has been made.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;ticket-refunds:7d11b95da6f13f352e32f5af2c24f251&#34;&gt;Ticket Refunds&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;layman-terms&#34;&gt;In which the conditions governing the refund of tickets are detailed.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The User must be sure of their intentions before making a purchase because the refund of purchased tickets is not allowed. Failure to attend a performance or a mistake on the purchase of tickets are not valid reasons for a refund. Tickets can only be canceled for technical or operational reasons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is important to emphasize that Extrema Sistemas acts as an agent and not as a seller. In the case of event cancellation, the User must get in contact with the Organizer to obtain information about their eligibility for a refund. In case of postponement or rescheduling of the event, the Organizer may establish refund limitations. The maximum amount of a refund will be the nominal value of the entry on the date of acquisition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is the responsibility of the User to know whether an event is canceled or the date and time of any rescheduled event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Purchased tickets are subject to management fees for ticketing and order processing fees that in no case are refundable. Refunds will be limited to a maximum number of tickets per event to each User.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;duration-and-termination:7d11b95da6f13f352e32f5af2c24f251&#34;&gt;Duration and Termination&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;layman-terms&#34;&gt;In which the duration of these legal conditions is measured as well as the right of Extrema Sistemas to remove conflicting contents.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The term of this Legal Agreement is indefinite. Extrema Sistemas may terminate or suspend the availability of any content if it is understood that violates these Terms and Conditions as well as suspend the account of the user responsible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If any of the clauses mentioned above are invalid or against Law, it will be considered as not included, all the others remaining valid and with full effectiveness for the parties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;applicable-law:7d11b95da6f13f352e32f5af2c24f251&#34;&gt;Applicable Law&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;layman-terms&#34;&gt;We remain reasonable and open to discussion, but in Madrid.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The User agrees that this Agreement is governed by the laws of Spain. The User agrees to submit to the jurisdiction of the courts located in Comunidad de Madrid, Spain for the purpose of litigating all such claims.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;additional-resources:7d11b95da6f13f352e32f5af2c24f251&#34;&gt;Additional Resources&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/about/privacy/&#34;&gt;Learn more about our Privacy Policy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legal (Spanish)</title>
      <link>/about/legal-es/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 20:14:03 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/legal-es/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Esta página introduce los Términos y Condiciones de Koliseo, una plataforma que permite gestionar la agenda, feedback y entradas para tu eventos. &lt;a href=&#34;/about/legal/&#34;&gt;Ir a la versión en Inglés&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;identificación-de-la-empresa:e940303d3b1b03019cae484e0f62c1b6&#34;&gt;Identificación de la empresa&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;layman-terms&#34;&gt;En la que explicamos quiénes somos, y dónde se nos puede encontrar&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Extrema Sistemas, S.L., titular del sitio web &lt;a href=&#34;http://koliseo.com&#34;&gt;http://koliseo.com&lt;/a&gt; (en adelante Koliseo) con domicilio en la Calle Casas de Miravete 24A, 28031 Madrid; provista de CIF B38676615, inscrita en el registro mercantil de la Comunidad de Madrid, Tomo 29.041, folio 109, sección 8, hoja M-522980, inscripción octava (en adelante Extrema Sistemas).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Las presentes condiciones regulan el acceso y el uso del servicio que Koliseo pone a disposición de los Usuarios de Internet. Cualquier consulta puede dirigirse a través de la dirección: info@koliseo.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;aceptación-de-las-condiciones-de-uso:e940303d3b1b03019cae484e0f62c1b6&#34;&gt;Aceptación de las condiciones de uso&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;layman-terms&#34;&gt;En la que dejamos claro que para poder utilizar este sitio web primero deben aceptarse estas condiciones&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Las personas que hagan uso de Koliseo (en adelante Usuarios) deberán leer las presentes Condiciones Generales de Uso. El uso o acceso a Koliseo implica el conocimiento y la plena aceptación de las advertencias legales y condiciones que a continuación se detallan. Extrema Sistemas se reserva el derecho a modificar las presentes Condiciones de Uso bajo iniciativa propia y sin necesidad de previo aviso al Usuario, entrando en vigor dichas condiciones desde el momento de su publicación en la web y de aplicación retroactiva.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Extrema Sistemas se reserva el derecho a modificar sin previo aviso el diseño, presentación y configuración del sitio web, así como los servicios nuevos o existentes. Asimismo, Extrema Sistemas se reserva el derecho de, en cualquier momento y sin necesidad de previo aviso, denegar el acceso a este sitio a aquellos Usuarios que incumplan cualesquiera de estas condiciones legales o de las particulares que les sean de aplicación.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;La aceptación del presente aviso legal supone la creación de un Acuerdo Legal con efectos vinculantes entre Extrema Sistemas y el Usuario. Al utilizar Koliseo, el Usuario acepta los Términos y Condiciones de Usuario (en adelante, Términos y Condiciones) que a continuación se establecen, y acepta que tiene capacidad legal para celebrar y responder por el presente Acuerdo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;objetivo-del-website:e940303d3b1b03019cae484e0f62c1b6&#34;&gt;Objetivo del website&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;layman-terms&#34;&gt;En la que se explica que nuestro objetivo es vender entradas y favorecer la interacción entre usuarios.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nuestro objetivo es ofrecer a los Usuarios de Koliseo la mejor experiencia posible en la compra de entradas de eventos. Dicha experiencia va acompañada de herramientas de gestión de eventos y funcionalidades para la compartición de opiniones con el resto de Usuarios.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Extrema Sistemas actúa como agente de venta de entradas autorizado, vendiendo entradas en nombre del promotor (en adelante Promotor) que organiza el evento para el que el Usuario adquiere una entrada. Extrema Sistemas puede compartir con el Promotor los datos personales de Usuarios que han adquirido entradas. Extrema Sistemas puede utilizar los datos del Usuario para ponerse en contacto con él cuando sea necesario en relación con las transacciones realizadas por el Usuario en Koliseo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;obligaciones-del-usuario:e940303d3b1b03019cae484e0f62c1b6&#34;&gt;Obligaciones del Usuario&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;layman-terms&#34;&gt;En la que se especifica el límite de edad y los usos permitidos en Koliseo. No se permite enviar spam, difundir contenidos que atenten contra la moral ni realizar reventa de entradas. Ante la duda, el sentido común suele ir bien.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;darse-de-alta-en-el-sistema:e940303d3b1b03019cae484e0f62c1b6&#34;&gt;Darse de alta en el sistema&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Koliseo no almacena credenciales, y delega en terceros la autenticación de los usuarios. El servidor crea la cuenta de usuario automáticamente la primera vez que un usuario abre sesión en el sistema. La página de log-in especifica claramente que abrir una sesión de usuario implica la aceptación de estos Términos y Condiciones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;La edad mínima para poder hacer uso de Koliseo son los 14 años de edad. Los niños menores de edad siempre deben solicitar y obtener el permiso de sus padres, de su tutor o de su representante legal antes de poder acceder a Koliseo. Queda prohibido el acceso y uso a los menores de edad no autorizados. Extrema Sistemas entiende que cuando un menor de edad accede a Koliseo cuenta con el permiso de sus padres, de su tutor o de su representante legal. Como responsable legal de los menores a su cargo, recuerde que los contenidos y servicios que se incorporan en Koliseo están dirigidos a una audiencia diversa y por consiguiente pueden existir determinadas áreas o secciones que pudieran incorporar contenidos o comentarios no apropiados a los menores de edad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Extrema Sistemas no puede validar la veracidad de los datos introducidos y no se hace responsable de que posibles Usuarios falseen los datos. Extrema Sistemas bloqueará el acceso a todos aquellos Usuarios que se demuestre que no cumplen la edad mínima legal o que han falseado cualquier otro dato.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;información-personal:e940303d3b1b03019cae484e0f62c1b6&#34;&gt;Información personal&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Koliseo almacena datos personales necesarios para realizar nuestras funciones. Puedes leer más sobre &lt;a href=&#34;/about/privacy/&#34;&gt;nuestra Política de Privacidad (en inglés)&lt;/a&gt;, incluyendo nuestro uso de Cookies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cuando El Usuario se registra para un evento está dando tu consentimiento para proveer de sus datos personales al organizador del evento, que no está sujeto a las presentes Condiciones Legales. Extrema Sistemas no es responsable de las acciones de estos organizadores con respecto a tus datos personales.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;compra-de-entradas:e940303d3b1b03019cae484e0f62c1b6&#34;&gt;Compra de entradas&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Para poder realizar la compra de entradas el Usuario declara ser mayor de edad (18 años o más, dependiendo de la legislación aplicable) y disponer de capacidad legal necesaria para la compra de entradas a través de Koliseo, manifestando asimismo que acepta la vinculación a este Acuerdo y entiende y acepta en su totalidad las condiciones aquí enunciadas para utilizar este website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;El recinto se reserva el derecho de admisión en caso de que el Usuario infrinja alguna norma del recinto. De forma puntual, el recinto podrá realizar inspecciones de seguridad para garantizar la seguridad de los clientes. Los Usuarios que lleguen con retraso serán acomodados durante un descanso apropiado del evento, pero la admisión no estará garantizada en este caso. La empresa no se hará responsable de ninguna pérdida o robo de entradas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;uso-no-permitido:e940303d3b1b03019cae484e0f62c1b6&#34;&gt;Uso no permitido&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;El Usuario se compromete a utilizar los servicios aportados por Koliseo de conformidad con la Ley y los presentes Términos y Condiciones, debiendo abstenerse de emplearlos para:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Transmitir a terceros no autorizados su nombre de usuario y su contraseña.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Introducir en la red programas informáticos susceptibles de provocar daños en los sistemas informáticos de Koliseo, sus proveedores o terceros.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Realizar actividades ilícitas o contrarias a la buena fe, a las costumbres, a la moral o al orden público.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Realizar actividades que constituyan una infracción de la regulación sobre propiedad intelectual e industrial o cualquier otra norma del ordenamiento jurídico aplicable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Difundir contenidos de carácter racista, xenófobo, pornográfico, erótico, de apología del terrorismo y/o que atenten contra los derechos humanos.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Acosar a otra persona.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Realizar prácticas de spamming y, en general, difundir publicidad no solicitada o autorizada, material publicitario, &amp;ldquo;correo basura&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;cartas en cadena&amp;rdquo;,
&amp;ldquo;estructuras piramidales&amp;rdquo;, o cualquier otra forma de información.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Involucrar en actividades comerciales sin consentimiento expreso por parte de Extrema Sistemas. Serán consideradas como actividades comerciales los trueques,
apuestas, publicidad, reventa de entradas, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;El Usuario entiende y acepta que sin aviso previo Extrema Sistemas puede interrumpir su acceso a Koliseo, cancelar sus entradas o eliminar cualquier contenido del Usuario si Extrema Sistemas entiende que dicho contenido ha infringido o no es coherente con
estos Términos y Condiciones o constituye una infracción de los derechos de Extrema Sistemas, de otros Usuarios o de la ley.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;exclusión-de-responsabilidades:e940303d3b1b03019cae484e0f62c1b6&#34;&gt;Exclusión de responsabilidades&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;layman-terms&#34;&gt;En la que dejamos claro que meteremos el cuezo porque este sistema está desarrollado por humanos. Pero seguimos trabajando para que nuestros errores se limiten a ser una anécdota graciosa.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;El Usuario reconoce que técnicamente no es posible lograr disponibilidad de Koliseo al 100%. Extrema Sistemas no garantiza la disponibilidad y continuidad del servicio. Extrema Sistemas excluye cualquier tipo de responsabilidad por los daños y perjuicios de toda naturaleza que puedan deberse a la falta de disponibilidad o al uso fraudulento que los Usuarios hubieran podido hacer del website. Extrema Sistemas no asumirá ningún tipo de responsabilidad por los posibles fallos en el acceso a las páginas de Koliseo. No obstante, Extrema Sistemas se esforzará por mantener la disponibilidad de Koliseo de la forma más continua posible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Extrema Sistemas no puede asegurar que los archivos que descargue el Usuario no contengan virus o archivos maliciosos. Extrema Sistemas no se responsabilizará por los daños que puedan deberse al uso de Koliseo, incluidos sin limitación, daños directos, indirectos, incidentales, punitivos y consecuentes. Extrema Sistemas no es responsable de los productos, servicios, acciones o falta de acción de cualquier recinto, artista, promotor o tercero en relación con Koliseo o al que se haya hecho referencia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;devoluciones-de-entradas:e940303d3b1b03019cae484e0f62c1b6&#34;&gt;Devoluciones de entradas&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;layman-terms&#34;&gt;En la que se detallan las condiciones de devolución del importe de las entradas.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;El Usuario debe estar seguro de sus intenciones antes de realizar una compra ya que no se permite la devolución de entradas adquiridas. La imposibilidad de asistir a una actuación o un error al realizar la adquisición de entradas no son motivos válidos de devolución. Sólo se pueden cancelar entradas por motivos técnicos u operativos.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Es importante recalcar que Extrema Sistemas actúa en calidad agente y no de vendedor. En los casos de cancelación del evento, el Usuario deberá ponerse en contacto con el Promotor para obtener información acerca de si tiene derecho a recibir el reembolso. En caso de posponer o programar de nuevo el evento, el Promotor puede establecer limitaciones de reembolso. El importe máximo de reembolso será el valor nominal de la entrada en la fecha de adquisición.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Es responsabilidad del Usuario informarse de si se ha cancelado un evento o la fecha y hora de cualquier evento pospuesto.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Las entradas compradas están sujetas a cargos por gestión de venta de entradas y a cargos por tramitación de pedidos que en ningún caso serán reembolsables. Se limitará un número máximo de entradas por evento a cada Usuario.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;duración-y-terminación:e940303d3b1b03019cae484e0f62c1b6&#34;&gt;Duración y terminación&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;layman-terms&#34;&gt;En la que se mide la duración de estas condiciones legales así como el derecho de Extrema Sistemas a retirar contenidos que las infrinjan.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;La duración del presente Acuerdo Legal es indefinida. Extrema Sistemas podrá dar por terminado o suspender la accesibilidad de cualquier contenido si se entiende que viola estos Términos y Condiciones, así como suspender la cuenta del usuario responsable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cualquiera de las cláusulas anteriores que sea nula o fuera contraria a La Ley, se tendrá como no puesta, quedando las demás en vigor y con plena eficacia para las partes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;legislación-aplicable:e940303d3b1b03019cae484e0f62c1b6&#34;&gt;Legislación aplicable&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;layman-terms&#34;&gt;En la que se explica que somos razonables y estamos dispuestos a hablar, pero en Madrid.&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Este acuerdo se rige por la legislación de España. Serán competentes para conocer de las divergencias que se deriven de la interpretación o aplicación de estas condiciones los Jueces y Tribunales de la Comunidad de Madrid. En caso de litigio las partes acuerdan, con renuncia al fuero que pudiera corresponderles, que la competencia judicial corresponderá a los Jueces y Tribunales de La Comunidad de Madrid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;recursos-adicionales:e940303d3b1b03019cae484e0f62c1b6&#34;&gt;Recursos Adicionales&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/about/privacy/&#34;&gt;Lee acerca de nuestra Política de Privacidad (en inglés)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>/about/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 20:14:03 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/privacy/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;We collect information to provide better services to all of our users. This page explains what information we collect and why we collect it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;information-that-we-collect:18d05a63a1c8d7ed973cc51838494e41&#34;&gt;Information that we collect&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We collect information in the following ways:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Information you introduce in the platform manually&lt;/strong&gt;. For example, you may enter your Twitter account or a user description on your user profile page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Information we get from your Authentication provider&lt;/strong&gt;. When you log into the platform for the first time we get the following information from your authentication provider: &lt;strong&gt;OAuth id&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Name&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;E-mail address&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;Photo&lt;/strong&gt;. We use this information to identify and contact you in case an event that you are attending or organizing is suffering changes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Logs&lt;/strong&gt;. When you use our services, we automatically collect and store information in server logs, including:

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The pages that you visited.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your IP address.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some limited information provided by your browser such as browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request, and referral URL.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Local storage&lt;/strong&gt;. We may collect and store information locally in your browser using HTML5 technologies to improve the web page performance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cookies&lt;/strong&gt;. We use cookies to store your user session and to aggregate user visits (using Google Analytics) to help us improve our services. Your event organizer may introduce their own Google Analytics information to track visits to their event pages as well.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may configure your browser to block cookies from our website. However, many of our services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. For example, you will not be able to log in if cookies are not enabled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;information-we-do-not-have-access-to:18d05a63a1c8d7ed973cc51838494e41&#34;&gt;Information we do not have access to&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Specifically, we do not get access to this information:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Personal information from your OAuth provider other than specified above&lt;/strong&gt;. Specifically, we do not have access to your password, list of contacts on social networks, or activity on other websites. Koliseo does not gain permission to do actions on your behalf, other than to retrieve the information detailed above.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Credit card information&lt;/strong&gt;. When accepting payments, we delegate to a third-party for payment processing. During this process, Koliseo does not have access to your credit card details.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;sharing-with-third-parties:18d05a63a1c8d7ed973cc51838494e41&#34;&gt;Sharing with third parties&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We do not share personal information with third parties unless one of the following circumstances applies:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;With your consent&lt;/strong&gt;. Some event organizers may ask to add the information of their attendees to a communications list. In such a case, we require opt-in consent during the ticket purchase process before sharing sensitive personal information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;With our event organizers&lt;/strong&gt;. We may only share the amount of information required by event organizers to be able to contact you for updates about events that you are attending to.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Anonymized information&lt;/strong&gt;. We track anonymized data about visits to our website. We may share parts of this anonymized information with event organizers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For legal reasons&lt;/strong&gt;. We will share personal information if reasonably necessary to:

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Meet any applicable law or legal process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Protect against harm our users or the public as required or permitted by law.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;security:18d05a63a1c8d7ed973cc51838494e41&#34;&gt;Security&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We work to protect your data from unauthorized access:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We encrypt our services using SSL.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We delegate to secure third-party providers your user credentials, so that Koliseo does not have access to your username and password.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We delegate the handling of your credit card details to secure, specialized third-party processing platforms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We store our data in one of the most secure Cloud providers, which add extra layers of physical and logical protection.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;changes:18d05a63a1c8d7ed973cc51838494e41&#34;&gt;Changes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our Privacy Policy may change. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of privacy policy changes).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/_index/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 00:01:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/_index/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>